You mean
you and I team up
to make Gao Yayan marry me?
Why?
Is there a problem?
Of course there is.
Don't think I don't know
about your relationship with Gao Yayan.
What relationship?
You're a couple.
I know
she likes you.
But let me tell you...
That's just on the surface.
On the surface?
Then what's the reality?
I'm using her.
Using her?
My dream is dance drama.
My stage is in Beijing,
in the Golden Hall of Vienna,
but definitely not in Checheng.
And Gao Yayan
is the first step to realizing my dream.
So,
I achieve my dream,
you marry into the Gao family,
and we both get what we want.
Mr. Feng,
you can do the math,
right?
In the last moments of her life,
Shen Xi left the choice to me.
I could burn this letter,
or I could hand it over to the police.
She said if I burned this letter,
she would wish us
a lifetime of happiness.
Guess
what I'll choose.
I don't know what you'll choose.
But Gao Yayan,
ask yourself.
When you chose to invest in me
and be with me,
wasn't it partly
to rebel against your dad?
What kind of man was your dad?
He forced you to give up
your dancing dream
and get engaged to someone
you didn't love.
He even fooled around with other women
right in front of your mom's portrait.
Did he not deserve it?
He had it coming.
It was your dad
who drove my dad to his death
and drove Shen Xi crazy.
Didn't you want
to escape his control too?
What's the point of saying all this now?
What's the use?
We are just using each other.
I just see things more clearly than you.
He deserved to die.
He had it coming.
Song Yanfei,
what makes you so self-righteous?
Do you think everyone is like you?
Let me tell you,
I have never
used you.
It's you.
You keep saying
what a beast
Gao Yuhai is,
but
you're doing the exact same things he did.
No,
you did worse than him.
You used me.
You used Shen Xi.
You used both of us,
who loved you so truly.
You're not a man.
You're a piece of trash.
Yayan,
Shen Xi did it all.
Do you understand?
Yanyan.
I only have you.
You're all I have in this world.
I swear,
I really thought about
letting go of the hatred
and being with you.
But I couldn't.
I just couldn't.
Yanyan,
your dad really killed my dad.
I had to avenge my dad.
I had no choice.
But it's fine now.
Gao Yuhai is dead.
Can't we just be together?
Why do we have to be like this?
Let's let each other go,
okay?
Let you go?
Will the dead Shen Xi let you go?
Who will let me go?
Okay.
Now let's talk about your choices.
You can hand this letter
over to the police.
And then what?
Your father's scandal,
Shen Xi's ordeal,
and the fact
that you transferred assets for me
will all be exposed.
Wending Group's stock price will plummet.
Your position as the heir
will be in jeopardy.
You will lose everything.
Do you understand?
Are you
threatening me?
I'm just weighing
the pros and cons with you.
Yanyan,
Okay.
our feelings for each other are real,
right?
Our connection is real.
Our dance drama is real too.
You have to believe me.
Gao Yuhai is already dead.
Let's not do this anymore.
You need me to manage Wending Group,
right?
The dance drama tour is also your dream,
Why are you doing this?
It seems
I never
really knew you.
I thought it would be over
once you got your revenge.
So I gritted my teeth
and forced myself to understand you.
Then came Xiao Ze.
I continued to turn a blind eye.
But today,
I suddenly realized
I was wrong.
I misjudged you.
You are an absolute monster.
You are completely consumed by hatred.
Your hatred will never end.
You will only take our true feelings...
Trampling on these lives
so casually,
Song Yanfei,
you don't deserve it.
You don't deserve it.
Shen Xi killed your dad.
Remember,
I didn't kill your dad.
No, it's not true.
Shen Xi killed your dad.
Your dad deserved to die.
You did all of this.
Do you think this
will lessen your guilt?
It's not like that.
Do you believe in karma?
Do you?
I do.
Ridiculous.
I do,
so I won't keep making mistakes with you.
I was wrong before.
But now I have
something more important to protect.
This is
the greatest punishment for you.
Shen Xi wrote this to you.
If you won't read it,
I'll read it to you.
Yanfei,
do you know?
I've also been wondering
if that so-called chance encounter
at the Cultural Palace
was a long-awaited reunion,
or your elaborate scheme.
But the more I think about it,
the more scared I get.
If that's really the case,
Shen Xi,
then you're truly terrifying.
I can't imagine
that the person
who encouraged me to compete
and the one who ultimately stopped me
from winning the championship
are the same person.
And it just so happens that this person
is the one I love the most.
Funny, isn't it?
Whether it's true or not,
thinking like this
makes me a fool, right?
It doesn't matter.
Since I'm already your little fool,
I might as well be one to the end.
What do Shen Xi and I have in common?
It's that
what you thought was our ignorance
was actually our willingness
after knowing everything.
If you, Song Yanfei,
could have just one moment
of willingness without hatred
in your life,
I hope
it's your willingness to turn yourself in.
Turn myself in?
I'll turn myself in.
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
It's good
that you're the one arresting me.
Yayan,
we came here today
for two main purposes.
First,
to check on your condition.
Seeing you're fine
puts our minds at ease.
Second,
we are currently investigating
Song Yanfei's case.
I'd like to ask
if you have any other clues
for us
besides that suicide note.
We'll be leaving now.
Get some rest.
Thank you.
Captain Li,
I actually have one more thing
to give you.
But as for
whether it's useful,
and whether to bring it up,
I'll leave it up to you.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself.
We're leaving.
Get Captain Li here,
or I won't say a word.
Song Yanfei,
watch your tone.
Cut the crap.
Get Li Xingchen here.
Song Yanfei,
you're already sitting here.
Confessing is
your smartest move right now.
Get Li Xingchen here.
Did you use me?
I guess so.
Do you regret it?
My dad is dead.
You should know that best.
Xingchen,
have you ever held someone's ashes?
When I held my dad's ashes,
they were much lighter than I imagined.
When I saw my dad's
life's work
destroyed just like that,
watching his enemies
toasting and
thriving in
his old office,
that's when you realize
dreams and
promises are
all bullshit.
Nothing compares to hatred.
I want Gao Yuhai dead.
Li Xingchen: Yu Xiaotong
Song Yanfei: Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
Shen Xi: Xie Tiantian
Special Appearance
(in order of strokes of Chinese surname)
Xiao Ze: Wang Hao
Jiang Dahai: Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Mu Liyan: Chen Yongxia
Weng Wei: Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Zhou Qinpeng
Gao Yuhai: Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Trace Evidence Officer: Kang Hairu
Li Xingchen's Classmate
Xiao Bai / Xiao Si: Zhang Weilun
Zha Minxin
Li Xingchen's Classmate: Gao Jing
Special / Extras
Xiao Ze's Mother: Zhao Yue'en
Xiao Ze's Relative Li Ming: Wang Zhilei
Assistant: Bai Zhihao
Dancers: Liu Yuxin, Yang Jiayue
Shi Jiaxin
Li Xingchen's Mother: Dong Dong
Special Female Classmate: Yue Yue
Li Xingchen's Classmate: Tang
Secretary: Qian Duoduo
Dai Mu: Wang Chunyang
Xia Youzhen
Fengshu's Secretary
Liu Ran
Waiters: Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Aunties: Tu Manxia, Huang Xinyang
Middle-aged Man: Wang Xinda
Driver Lao Zhao: Wei Hong
Surveillance Officer: Qin Zhiqiang
Xiao Ze's Father: Zhou Wen
Stagehand Xiao Zhang: Li Chen
Speaking Girl: Yue Yue
Police Colleague: Li Lijun
Receptionist Teacher: Ren Jiefei
Mr. Zhao: Liu Junjie
Driver: Hu Huazheng
Scrapyard Boss Zhang: Li Chenghu
Crane Operator: Liu Haitao
Yan's Father: Li Tianjun
Male Doctor: Wang Keming
Bai Wanting
Voice Actor
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in: Zhao
Lao Zhou
Forensic Doctor Zhou Wen: Pei Xiao
Cleaner: Liu Li
Extras: Da Qing, Liu Haohan
Receptionist Xiaoyu: Ren Jiefei
Chief Presenter: Xu Yue
Presenters: Sui Dalong, Yu Tianhang
Co-Presenters: Feng Fei, Guo Zhiyuan
Chief Planner: Li Meina
Consultant: Bai Di
Production Team
Hu Kaichen
Planner: Zhao
Yin Zhongheng
Line Producer: Hu Huazheng
Finance: Geng Yusa
Set Operations Team
Set Operations Lead: Liu Yiqing
Yang Qunbao
Catering
Catering Manager: Yin Xiumei
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Zhang Meijuan, Zheng Xiaorong
Zhang Kai, Liang Hui
Li Xiaojun, Song Shuwei
Hu Lei, Qiao Xueyue
Xiao Yucai
Co-Director: Xu Yue
Assistant to Director:
Tang Yuye, Li Gaoyang
On-Set Deputy Director: Liu Haohan
Casting Director: Dai Guoming
Editing Team
Sound Director: Zhang Kai
Co-Art Director: Gong Xueyuan
Prop Art: Zhang Xueqi
Props: Wu Tai
Set Dressers: Zhang Li, Zhang Qingzhong
Camera A Operator: He Yong
Camera A Assistant: Li Xinghan
Camera B Operator: Zhao Shidian
Camera C Operator: Ma Mingguo
Lighting Team
Lighting Director: Gao Yun
Terigun
Styling Team
Styling Director: Gao Bin
On-Set Hair & Makeup Lead: Li Zixu
On-Set Wardrobe:
Zhang Tingting, Qiu Yaqiong
Promotion & Distribution Team
Marketing Director: Li Yiyi
Planning Director: Yang Liuting
Project Coordinator: Zhao Zihan
Copywriters: Zhang Weirui, Li Ziwei
Graphic Designers: Ren Zhongjun, Shi Qi
Beijing Wenhui Qiming
Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Supervisor
Colorist: Niu Xue
End Credits: Jin Linxin
Subtitle Production: Su Li
Re-Recording Mixer: Zhang Kai
Sound Effects Editor: Zhang Xiaoman
Visual Effects
Jin Linxin
Zhang Qichun, Jin
Shang Chenyao
Music Production
Beijing Landuo Music
Music Director
Score Director: Xiao Zhuang
Music Editors: Jiang Zheng, Ma Ziting
Female Humming: Ma Qianran
Vocal Recording: Zheng Suyang
"Brothers"
Vocals: Yue Shunming
Composer: Xiao Zhuang
Yu Xiaotong
Lyrics
Music by Xiao Zhuang
Produced by Xiao Zhuang
"Promise"
Performed by Zhang Keying
Arranged by Xiao Zhuang
Performed by Ben Damiao
Lyrics by Xu Yue
Music by Xu Yue
"That's All"
Performed by Xu Yue
Music by Xu Yue
Arranged by Wang Anyu
Performed by Xu Yue
Lyrics by Fan Fan
Produced by Xu Yue
"The More I Love, The More I'm Wrong"
Bai Yuxiang
Produced by Xiao Zhuang
"Only You" (Russian)
Music by Xiao Zhuang
Arranged by Zhao Yi
Special Thanks
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Fangxian Lulingwang Liquor Co., Ltd.
Hubei Jiutouniao Catering
Management Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Sinopharm Dongfeng Huaguo Hospital
Shiyan Xiaowujia Catering
Management Service Co., Ltd.
Hubei Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Jindian Marketing
Management Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Mingxinhuizhi Dance Academy
Sina Entertainment Weibo TV Drama, Sina TV
Co-production Companies
Co-presenters
Shanxi Chengyi Film
and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Songyuan Senchengda Economic
and Trade Co., Ltd.